[
    {
      "question": "私は_____.",
      "answer": "道に迷いました",
      "options": ["道に迷いました", "駅", "地図", "左"]
    },
    {
      "question": "____はどこですか？",
      "answer": "駅",
      "options": ["地図", "駅", "右", "左"]
    },
    {
      "question": "____を見せてください。",
      "answer": "地図",
      "options": ["道に迷いました", "地図", "まっすぐ", "迷子センター"]
    },
    {
      "question": "右に____ください。",
      "answer": "曲がって",
      "options": ["進んで", "曲がって", "まっすぐ", "助けてください"]
    },
    {
      "question": "左に____ください。",
      "answer": "行って",
      "options": ["進んで", "行って", "右", "まっすぐ"]
    },
    {
      "question": "まっすぐ____ください。",
      "answer": "進んで",
      "options": ["進んで", "曲がって", "行って", "道に迷いました"]
    },
    {
      "question": "この近くに____はありますか？",
      "answer": "コンビニ",
      "options": ["道に迷いました", "迷子センター", "コンビニ", "地図"]
    },
    {
      "question": "迷子センターは____ですか？",
      "answer": "どこ",
      "options": ["どこ", "どこですか", "まっすぐ", "助けてください"]
    },
    {
      "question": "私は____です。",
      "answer": "迷子",
      "options": ["迷子", "左", "駅", "地図"]
    },
    {
      "question": "____はどこですか？",
      "answer": "迷子センター",
      "options": ["迷子センター", "道", "駅", "右"]
    }
  ]
  